{"data":[{"question":"A passer-by caught the shoplifter and took him to the local police station.     -> The shoplifter .................... by a passer-by and taken to the local police station.\n","answer":"was caught","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"4"},{"question":"The hotel management requests the guests to leave the rooms by midday.     -> The guests ....................... to leave the rooms by midday.\n","answer":"are requested","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"4"},{"question":"Where did they hide all the sports equipment?     -> Where ......................... all the sports equipment hidden?\n","answer":"was","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"4"},{"question":"Tourists don't visit this museum very often.     -> This museum ......................... very often by tourists.\n","answer":"isn't visited","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"4"},{"question":"How often does he re-install his computer?How often is his computer.........................?\n","answer":"re-installed","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"4"},{"question":"In the first stage of the process they roast and grind coffee beans.     -> Coffee beans ........................ in the first stage of the process.\n","answer":"are roasted and ground","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"4"},{"question":"The Polish archaeologists were the first to excavate and describe this temple.     -> This temple ....................... by the Polish archaeologists.\n","answer":"was first excavated and described","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"4"},{"question":"The professor reminded the students about the due-date for handing essays.     -> The students ....................... about the due-date for handing essays.\n","answer":"were reminded","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"4"},{"question":"People speak English all over the world.     -> English ........................... all over the world.\n","answer":"is spoken","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"4"},{"question":"They do not permit smoking in the auditorium.     -> Smoking ........................... in auditorium.\n","answer":"isn't permitted","category":"1","subcategorylv1":"56","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"4"}]}